♪ Pink hands so fine ♪
♪ Gold-branded wine ♪
♪ Spring paints willows green;
palace walls can't confine ♪
♪ East wind unfair ♪
♪ Happy times rare ♪
♪ In my heart, sad thoughts throng ♪
♪ We've severed for years long ♪
♪ Wrong, wrong, wrong ♪
Si Jin
Episode 24
Come here!
Take shelter here.
Careful.
Get on.
It's raining heavily.
The palace gates are about to close.
Are you going out?
Yes.
(Princess Fuqing)
Is it bustling outside?
Of course.
Much more so than in the Palace,
especially at the Lantern Festival
in the West Market.
There are all kinds of lanterns.
They're amazing.
Also, the fireworks
are breathtaking.
You have to
see for yourself someday.
Have you never seen them?
The rain is about to stop.
I'll walk you out.
Uh...
is it too much trouble?
Not at all.
Thank you then.
Princess Fuqing?
(Is she that princess)
(who's said to have eye disease?)
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness,
I've finally found you.
Are you alright?
Greetings, sir.
Your Highness, I was so worried
when the rain poured down just now.
Please don't ever
go out alone again.
Your Highness.
I failed to recognize you earlier.
I'm sorry
for my rudeness.
It's fine.
No one had ever said that.
They had never told me
about those fun things to see and do
in case I became upset.
Ms. Hua,
he's leaving.
Please walk him out for me.
Yes.
Let's go back, Your Highness.
Good night, Your Highness.
Miss!
Bad news, Miss!
Is Commandant Yu alright?
He's fine. It's Duke An's heir.
He died all of a sudden
when drinking with girls.
Died all of a sudden?
What about Qiaoniang?
I knew you'd be worried
and asked about her.
Everyone in Duke An's Mansion
is looking forward to her baby,
the sole lineal grandson
of great significance.
I hope Qiaoniang will be fine.
Ji Chongyi died...
(He had died much earlier last time.)
(I thought as things changed, )
(he'd live, )
(but he ended up the same.)
(It was probably his fate.)
Smells so good!
How long will it be done?
In a second.
Taste it, Zhan.
Is it good?
So rich and flavorful!
I... I want more.
Chief,
here come noodles. Let's eat.
No.
No?
Still waiting for Miss Si's fish soup?
Mind your own business
or those things in the office.
Fine. I won't get between you two.
I'll go once I'm done.
(Fragrance Shop)
Stop sighing,
or you'll drive away
all our clients.
Qi is a rare catch.
He's most reliable and charming.
He and Si make a perfect match.
Lift your arm.
So what?
My sister
deserves the best man in the world.
Be reasonable.
In all of Ling'an,
there's hardly anyone
better than Qi.
This side.
I disagree.
I think I'm
as good as him
if
not a tad better.
You...
What's that supposed to mean?
If you ask me,
people are different.
No need to compare yourself with others.
Ever since he and Si became close,
she's been paying
less and less attention to me.
It can't go on like this!
Look at you
being so jealous already.
When she
gets married,
won't you feel even worse?
Yu Jin.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
I'm here for something important.
Speak.
Aren't you going to let me in?
What if I speak up,
and everyone hears?
I don't mind, though.
The door's over there.
Yu Jin.
Are you living in this hut?
It's way beneath you.
When will Uncle reinstate you as prince?
I heard you two had met
at the Mid-Autumn Hunt.
What's your point?
Yu Jin,
my point is
we're family.
That dog bites,
Yu Jin!
Cui Mingyue, cut to the chase.
Then get out.
Yu Jin,
if that's your attitude,
I'll talk to Jiang Si instead.
Your Grace probably forgot
about my warning.
I remember
every word you've said.
Although you're mean to me,
I can't blame you.
But Jiang Si is different.
A humble earl's daughter
is no match for the Grand Princess.
If you...
If you obey me,
I won't give her a hard time.
Can we sit down and talk now?
There's nothing to talk about.
Here's my only advice.
Stay away from Jiang Si.
Some bravado you got, Prince Jin.
She still doesn't know
who you really are, right?
A prince is
way out of the league
of a powerless earl's daughter.
Yu Jin, your wife
should match your status,
who's noble
and well-connected.
Although Jiang Si is
good-looking
and seductive as her mother,
making men fall for her,
you should know
it's no more than a fling.
You two won't make it
even without me.
Who's there?
You should leave.
At ease.
Here you are being so caring and sweet.
Su seduced my father the same way, huh?
It was Commandant Yu
who made you mad.
Why vent your anger on me?
You said
my mother and I seduced men.
Your Grace,
why not try it yourself
and see if it'll work?
There aren't noble or dirty ways
as long as they work.
How shameless!
You think I was complimenting you?
You came alone,
insisting on chatting with Mr. Yu,
and threatened him to comply.
Weren't you trying to seduce him?
But he has no interest in you.
This is the first time I've seen
a girl harassing a man
when he asks her to leave.
A County Princess like you
is indeed bolder.
Clearly, a decent girl
like me is not your match.
Your Grace, will you leave,
or shall I make you go?
Stop.
You're the 7th Prince.
You crossed the line.
Just you wait.
Did you hear everything?
I'd tell you later.
I didn't mean to keep it from you.
Behave yourself, Prince Jin.
I apologize for not recognizing you
and offending you before.
Let's go, Aman.
Yu Jin, your wife
should match your status,
who's noble
and well-connected.
Eat now.
Eat it.
Are you on a fast like him?
You...
Chief,
stop splitting firewood
in the middle of the night.
Look,
we can fight on the battlefield,
but you can't do this.
Stop, please.
Chief, I'll help you.
I'll apologize to Miss Si for you.
Alright?
Wait, no.
Go with the ax.
Is it to kill?
I need you to tell her
not to bottle up her anger.
Vent it on me!
Relax, Chief.
Once she sees me,
she'll know your apology
is sincere.
I'm on it now.
Go.
This stab
is for my husband,
Yu Qi.
Why did you kill him, too?
Do you think
he's just that Yu Qi you know?
(Turns out, Yu Qi is)
(the 7th Prince, who's said to be cursed.)
(He never told me about that.)
(The Grand Princess, after learning)
(about his identity, )
(feared that he'd threaten her power.)
(She deprived him of his military power)
(and Chiyu Cavalry)
(before declaring him dead.)
(But her daughter)
(was in love with Yu Qi.)
(So, she kept him alive)
(but caged in the Palace.)
Are you still mad, Miss?
I can go through that hole
to see Commandant Yu,
no Prince Jin,
and beat him up
for you.
Who says I'm mad at him?
Actually, I'm mad at myself.
I'm mad that I
knew so little about him
and got kept in the dark for so long.
But
it hasn't been too long
since you two met, right?
You canceled the engagement.
Then he moved in
and...
I feel as if
it's as long as two lifetimes.
♪ Looking back, I recall our first encounter ♪
♪ Feelings remain but things are complicated ♪
♪ Thoughts replay ♪
♪ I can't make up my mind ♪
♪ Can I still make it through the long night ♪
♪ I fear that we'll part again ♪
♪ A piercing ache lingers within ♪
♪ Shattering the dreams ♪
♪ How many petals fell, I count ♪
♪ It equals the times I think about you ♪
♪ The past fades as old dreams return ♪
♪ How can I move on ♪
♪ I can't forget about you ♪
♪ However long the road is ♪
♪ If love is strong, one will have no fear ♪
♪ During my lifetime ♪
(Prince Qi's Mansion)
You're right, Your Highness.
The Crown Prince
and Grand Princess are close.
When following him last night,
I found a powerful official
going to her mansion
with him.
Who was it?
I'm sorry.
Crown Prince's guards saw me
before I could get a good look.
I had a narrow escape.
That man's identity is unknown yet.
Go back and rest.
Thanks, Your Highness.
Where's your mask?
Your Highness,
I must've dropped it in the fight.
It was my fault. Please forgive me.
Don't worry.
Your Highness, I think
no one saw my face.
He was trained for years.
What a shame.
Your Highness.
Bury him properly.
Give his family 100 taels of silver.
100 taels?
He served me for years.
He deserved it.
I wish I wouldn't need to pay a copper
as long as he lived.
It's our great honor to be at your disposal,
Your Highness.
What's this, darling?
(Everlasting Prosperity)
When I went to the Palace
to greet Mother earlier,
I learned that Jin had returned
from the South
and gone to the Capital Security Office.
(Princess Qi)
I took the liberty
of preparing this gift for you.
You know,
that's really thoughtful.
I was wondering
how to get close to him.
We haven't met for years.
Mother said
Father hadn't
reinstated his position.
Speaking of which,
I'm clueless as well.
Father called him back
but made him work undercover
in the Capital Security Office.
Why?
After serving in the military for so long,
he has gained prestige.
The Chiyu Cavalry trained by him
is considered formidable.
But in the past,
Father seemed to
forget about him.
Why did he suddenly...?
Maybe there are certain things
that no one can do
but him.
Zhen Heng of Capital Security
might be a tough one,
but he's a scholar after all.
He's incapable of harsh means.
To think Father
questioned Cao Xingyu himself.
Maybe
that was pushed by Jin.
I know little about court affairs,
but you and Jin are brothers.
You two are of the same mother.
You're closer than others for sure.
As you said,
he's highly respected in the military.
He can be of great help
to your future plan.
You have a point, darling.
Father called him back secretly.
That means the past
is the past.
Maybe he'll entrust Jin with important work.
It'll do us no harm
to win him over now.
I have an idea.
Why don't we hold
a family banquet to welcome him back?
I heard he didn't get married.
I can invite
some noble girls I know.
Jin and the girls can get to know each other.
What do you think?
Brilliant!
I can take this chance
to sound my brother out
and see if he's greedy for power, money,
or girls.
Er'niu!
I'm counting on you.
Go!
(Morning Drizzle)
Er'niu?
Look, Miss.
Bearing rods to apologize.
(Qi)
Jin.
Jin,
we're reunited.
Finally!
I prepared a gift for you.
Thanks, Prince Qi.
That's too polite of you.
Call me Zhang or Brother.
Brother.
I didn't know you had come back
or settled down in such a shack.
You've suffered too much.
Why don't you live with us
before receiving your title and mansion?
No, thanks.
I'm used to
living alone.
I don't want to
trouble you and your wife.
No trouble at all.
We're brothers.
Fine, I won't force you
if you don't want to move in.
But now that you're back,
we should at least get together
to catch up, right?
My wife has arranged a dinner banquet
to welcome you home.
I...
That's too extravagant.
I... I prefer solitude.
Yu Jin,
here in Ling'an,
it's necessary
to make connections
to keep a foothold.
(To the 7th Prince, Yu Jin)
Thanks, Brother.
I have to go to work.
Please excuse me.
Sure, go ahead.
See you at my mansion.
Chief,
are you going to Prince Qi's banquet?
Going there my foot!
Your Highness, My Lady,
invitations to tomorrow's banquet
have been prepared and sent to the guests
on the list.
Send one to
Earl Dongping's Mansion, too.
Yes.
Earl Dongping's Mansion?
Jiang Si is well-known in town
for her beauty.
But she made a fuss
in order not to
marry Duke An's heir.
Her name was impaired.
I fear Jin'll mistake it,
thinking we look down on him.
That's fine.
My biggest fear is
what if
he doesn't come.
You two are brothers.
He won't embarrass you in front of others.
I hope not.
(To Earl's Lineal Daughter, Jiang Si)
Mother,
Si shouldn't go.
We're talking about Prince Qi's banquet.
All the guests
are leading celebrities
in town.
If any of them takes an interest in Si,
she'll be in luck.
That's exactly why
I don't want her to
get involved in those prominent clans.
She'll suffer
if she's married into one.
You're worrying too much.
If it were before
when she was soft,
she'd probably have a hard time.
But ever since she almost drowned,
she's become way too tough.
We should be glad if she doesn't
make others suffer.
I'm afraid
none of those clans
will marry their heirs to her.
Good!
I won't marry her to them either!
My Lady, Miss Si is here.
Grandmother.
Father.
Aunt Xiao.
Si,
Fu told you about it, right?
Prince Qi's Mansion sent an invitation
to you to their banquet earlier.
You should be dressed up.
I have
a set of the finest emerald jewelry.
Take it when you leave.
Thanks, Grandmother,
but I won't
go to that banquet.
Even Prince Qi's Mansion
isn't good enough for you?
I have no desire
to be married into a distinguished clan.
I just want to live an ordinary life.
Good! That's my daughter.
Do you hear that?
Given that attitude,
none of those clans
will choose her.
I hate Long Dan!
Why isn't he here yet?
Aman!
Stop! Stay right here!
I'm not allowed to see you.
Aman,
come on. You're the best.
Tell me how we can
cheer Miss Si up.
Chief's so frustrated
that he splits firewood every day.
We've got more than enough for a year.
He doesn't eat
or sleep.
He's lost tons of weight.
It pains me to see him like that.
I'm begging you!
He lied to Miss Si.
He deserves it!
So do you for helping him.
Chief simply made
the same mistake
every man makes.
Why can't Miss Si let it go?
What?
- Long Dan!
- Listen,
she's invited to
Prince Qi's banquet.
We'll go and see
if every man is as terrible
as your chief!
Miss!
Go ahead. We won't stop you.
You said so yourself!
- We'll go!
- Stop them!
Aman, let's go.
She... she left.
Stop them, stop them, stop them!
I thought you said the opposite.
(Grand Princess's Mansion)
Aunt.
What's wrong this time?
Aunt, did you hear
that Jin had returned quietly
from the South?
He's been working undercover
in the Capital Security Office.
And he's brought down
Earl Changxing's Mansion.
Was all that Father's order?
What's his attitude
toward Jin?
Will he pose a threat to my heirdom...?
Don't panic.
As the Crown Prince,
you shall always remain calm.
How could I remain calm, Aunt?
Father's never satisfied with me.
I was appointed
Crown Prince
simply because I was
the late Empress's only son.
Zhang has been
challenging me over the years.
Now that
his brother, Jin, is back,
he'll gain great help, won't he?
Relax.
Yu Jin returned
without permission.
His Majesty had to cover for him
in case he was impeached.
Really?
Why would I lie?
Be seated.
But
he and Prince Qi are of the same mother.
He has great prestige in the Chiyu Cavalry.
We have to beware of him.
You're wise, Aunt.
I'll be cautious.
Aunt, without you,
I'd be so lost!
Aren't you sweet?
Mother!
So loud. Where are your manners?
Mingyue is still young
and naive.
Greetings, Cousin Lang.
Mother,
did you hear
that Prince Qi'd hold a banquet today
to welcome Prince Jin back?
Why the fuss?
Prince Qi also invited many girls
from prominent clans.
That's not to welcome Prince Jin back
but to choose a wife for him.
Among all the princes,
I've never seen Mingyue
being so interested in any of them.
Cousin Lang,
Mother,
you probably don't know.
That day,
after I fell into the Jinshui River,
it was Prince Jin who got me out.
So?
So...
I want him, too.
Do you like Yu Jin?
I always let you have your way
except for being with Yu Jin.
Why?
You and Consort Xian are enemies,
so I can't marry
someone I admire?
He's
a cursed prince.
He doesn't deserve your admiration.
You're old enough
to get married.
I've chosen
a few men for you.
Let me tell you about them.
Don't bother.
I just want Prince Jin.
Aunt,
Mingyue is still a naive girl.
It's normal to fall for someone.
You know,
Jin
grew up at the border.
He isn't close
to Prince Qi or Consort Xian.
Once he marries Mingyue,
won't we gain
huge support from him?
How many times have I said
not to involve Mingyue
in power struggle?
Crown Prince,
have you forgotten?
Sorry, Aunt.
I'll keep that in mind.
Guard.
Yes.
Watch my daughter closely
before Prince Qi's banquet ends.
She cannot go out.
Yes.
Please, Your Grace.
So unfair!
Aunt, Mingyue's spoiled.
She didn't mean what she said.
Don't take it to heart.
I'll talk some sense into her.
Yu Jin,
the 7th Prince...
Mingyue!
There you are.
Why weren't you inside
to be lectured by my mother?
Why did you come out?
I hate to see girls' tears the most,
not to mention you're my cousin.
Mother is so unreasonable.
I can't go out.
Can you go to that banquet for me, please?
Pretty please!
Alright, fine.
I'll go there
to sabotage it for you.
(Prince Qi's Mansion)
With little etiquette left,
even the rabble
can enter Prince Qi's Mansion.
Let me check
if that invitation is forged.
(Ji Fanghua, Duke An's 3rd Daughter)
What?
Princess Qi had it
sent to Miss Si.
What are you doing?
How dare a maid interrupt!
Clearly, no one in your house
has manners.
I shall
teach her a lesson.
You're mad because I canceled the engagement
with your brother
and trying to take revenge.
How absurd!
It was my brother
who abandoned you, jinx!
Let bygones be bygones.
(Kou Lingbo, Granddaughter
of Grand Preceptor Kou)
Let me see.
Princess Qi is my cousin.
This doesn't match her handwriting.
She is indeed suspicious.
I knew it.
How could a humble girl like her
be invited to Prince Qi's Mansion?
Forgive me if I'm ignorant,
but I've never heard
that the hostess would
write invitations herself.
That's right.
Even in our humble abode,
we'd have the gatehouse do such work.
You...
Ling... Lingbo can't be wrong.
Is Princess Qi close to you
or her?
I don't know her,
but since she sent
an invitation to me,
she must've had her reason.
If you two insist
that I can't go in,
I shall explain everything to Princess Qi
in case she feels insulted,
thinking I have no manners.
Please send in a message for me
that Jiang Si
is kept outside by these two girls.
I'm unable to greet Princess Qi today.
Yes.
Wait!
Go ahead then.
Don't bluff!
Lingbo's grandfather is Grand Preceptor Kou.
Her uncle is the Vice Prime Minister
while your father is a mere 5th-rank earl.
If you sit with us,
won't you feel inferior?
So what if you're of noble birth?
You sound
even ruder than a boor.
Aman, let's go.
Yes.
(Prince Qi's Mansion)
(Everlasting Prosperity)
Everyone,
this banquet is to welcome
my brother, Jin, home.
Welcome back, Jin.
Let's toast to his return!
- Cheers.
- Hear! Hear!
The Crown Prince has arrived!
Greetings, Your Highness.
What now?
You invited all our brothers
but me, huh?
I'm simply having
a casual dinner with my brothers.
Am I not
your brother?
You're too busy, Your Highness.
I wouldn't dare disturb you.
Be seated.
Sit, everyone.
You're also here, Jin.
Your Highness.
Prince Qi,
this is your fault.
Why didn't you tell me?
Uh...
I made a lapse.
Please forgive me.
Jin,
we're brothers.
Although we've never met before,
no need to be too polite.
Yes, Your Highness.
Knowing that you came back,
I meant to
go with our brothers to drink with you.
But you don't
have a title or a mansion yet.
We don't have
a place to drink.
We can
drink anywhere
but not with anyone.
You mean it's the people,
not the place that matters, huh?
If we fail to
make Jin happy today,
we'll be to blame.
Am I right?
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes.
Let's
- get plastered with Jin!
- Good.
I appreciate
your kindness,
but I don't drink.
I'll toast you with tea instead.
Sorry for my negligence.
Serve tea.
I heard you
and your Chiyu Cavalry were invincible.
How could
a warrior like you be afraid of a drink?
Your Highness,
all eight of us
have finally got together.
Whether we drink liquor or tea,
our brotherhood remains
the same as ever.
If it's the same,
why drink tea?
What if
I must see
how much Ji can drink?
Jin,
please.
If you insist on making me drink,
I'll comply.
Ever since I joined the Chiyu Cavalry,
I've made a pledge not to drink
for the sake of warfare.
If I drink, I shall be
punished by military law.
If His Majesty got wind of this,
what would he think?
Never mind.
I wouldn't dare disobey your order.
I toast you, Lang.
Are you threatening me, Yu Jin?
I wouldn't dare.
I'm following your order
at the risk of my life.
Don't take it seriously.
I was joking with you.
(The End of Episode 24)
♪ From place to place ♪
♪ I drift in the world alone ♪
♪ The cool breeze comes and goes ♪
♪ I dare to love and hate ♪
♪ Ask the day and the night ♪
♪ If they saw a glimmer fall and take root ♪
♪ Growing between us ♪
♪ And breeding love ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ In the end, we're still together ♪
♪ Like shadows ♪
♪ We're brave enough to advance together ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ And stars ♪
♪ Don't ask what our fate is ♪
♪ Let life carve the growth rings ♪
♪ We'll reach the end eventually ♪
♪ All will bloom in spring ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ We travel at night in the cold ♪
♪ The moonlight shines like water ♪
♪ Those in love will have sweet dreams ♪
♪ Cherish each other in the future ♪
♪ Time goes by, but memories remain ♪
♪ Take a look to remember everything ♪
♪ We will see flowers fill the city again ♪